{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I go 'Meow' and like to chase string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk"},{"text":"🧶 I like to play with yarn"},{"text":"🐈 I have soft fur and whiskers"}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Woof Woof' and wag my tail. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I like to chew on bones"},{"text":"🎾 I love to play fetch"},{"text":"🏡 I am a good friend to have"}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I go 'Quack Quack' and like to swim in the pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌾 I like to eat bread"},{"text":"💦 I have webbed feet"},{"text":"🦆 I have a wide, flat bill"}],"options":[{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Moo' and give you milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌿 I eat grass in the field"},{"text":"⚫️ I have black and white spots"},{"text":"🐄 I live on a farm"}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I like to eat carrots and hop around. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I love to munch on vegetables"},{"text":"👂 I have long ears"},{"text":"🐰 I am a furry animal"}],"options":[{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fox","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I love to eat peanuts"},{"text":"🐘 I am very big and strong"},{"text":"🚿 I use my nose to spray water"}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I swing from trees and love bananas. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐒 I like to make funny faces"},{"text":"🌴 I live in the jungle"},{"text":"🐾 I have a long tail to help me balance"}],"options":[{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I roar loudly and have a big mane. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦁 I am the king of the jungle"},{"text":"🥩 I eat meat"},{"text":"🐾 I have sharp claws and teeth"}],"options":[{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I have black and white stripes and live in Africa. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦓 My stripes help me hide in tall grass"},{"text":"🐴 I look like a horse"},{"text":"🐾 I eat grass and plants"}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I have a long neck and eat leaves from tall trees. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦒 I am the tallest animal on Earth"},{"text":"🌍 I live in Africa"},{"text":"🐾 I have spots on my fur"}],"options":[{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Hippo","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rhino","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"transport":[{"level":"1","type":"transport","question":"I go beep beep! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚗 I have wheels."},{"text":"🚦 I drive on the road."},{"text":"👪 Mommy and Daddy drive me."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"2","type":"transport","question":"I go choo choo! I ride on a track. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚂 I am very long."},{"text":"👨‍✈️ I have a driver."},{"text":"🎫 People sit inside of me."}],"options":[{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Train","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"3","type":"transport","question":"I fly in the sky! I have wings. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✈️ I am very big."},{"text":"☁️ I go above the clouds."},{"text":"🌎 I can take you to different countries."}],"options":[{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ball","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Shoes","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"4","type":"transport","question":"I float on the water! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I travel on the sea."},{"text":"⚓ I have an anchor."},{"text":"🐠 Fish swim all around me."}],"options":[{"label":"Tree","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Spoon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"5","type":"transport","question":"I'm a big vehicle that helps people. I have a siren! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚨 I have a loud noise."},{"text":"🚑 I take people to the hospital."},{"text":"🤕 I help people when they are sick or hurt."}],"options":[{"label":"Ambulance","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"6","type":"transport","question":"I have two wheels and you pedal with your feet. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚲 I'm fun to ride outside."},{"text":"⛑️ You should wear a helmet when using me."},{"text":"🦵 You use your legs to make me go."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"7","type":"transport","question":"I'm a big truck that helps put out fires. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚒 I have a long hose."},{"text":"🔥 I help when something is burning."},{"text":"👨‍🚒 Firefighters ride in me."}],"options":[{"label":"Firetruck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Taxi","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"8","type":"transport","question":"I carry many children to school. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🏫 I am usually yellow."},{"text":"🛑 I stop to pick up children."},{"text":"👦👧 Children ride me to school."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tractor","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"9","type":"transport","question":"I can fly to the moon! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚀 I go very very high."},{"text":"👩‍🚀 Astronauts use me."},{"text":"🌌 I travel to outer space."}],"options":[{"label":"Rocket","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Motorbike","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"10","type":"transport","question":"I help farmers grow food. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚜 I am big and strong."},{"text":"🌾 I work in the fields."},{"text":"🧑‍🌾 Farmers use me to plow."}],"options":[{"label":"Tractor","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Skateboard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}}]}